I try to run when I can.
我一有机会就跑步，
I use an exercise bike.
我还骑健身自行车.
Those are the main aerobic forms of exercise,
有氧健身运动主要就是这两种方式.
then I do, er, dumbbell weights and sit-ups.
然后我还，er, 进行哑铃锻炼和做仰卧起坐.
I run or race-walk about, urn, about three miles, about five times a week.
我每星期跑步或竞走大概，urn,大概三英里, 大约五次.
Um, in addition to that I lift weights,
Um, 除此之外，我还举重，
er, 30 to 40 minutes about four times a week,
er, 30到40分钟，每个星期大约四次，
and for an hour and a half one time a week.
每个星期还会有一次是做一个半小时.
Actually, I run and then I'm going to go and lift weights, so...
我实际上是先跑步，然后去举重，所以...
I guess it comes out to be about two hours a day.
我想每天大概两小时左右吧.
I'm a triathlete,
我是名三项全能运动员，
so I have three disciplines that I have to train.
所以我必须接受三个项目的训练.
for cycling, swimming, and running,
这三个项目是骑白行车, 游泳和跑步.
so I try and do two a day.
所以我一般每天练两个项目.
So I park outside of the city
所以我是先把汽车停在城外，
and bicycle along the river here.
然后再沿着这条河骑自行车.
and I find when I do this, it's, er...
然后我发现我在做这项运动的时候，觉得它，er...
very therapeutic for my mind.
非常有益于大脑的健康.
I get pulled out of bed twice a week and,
每个星期有两次我会被从床上拉起来，
er, between seven and eight we do our loop here-it takes an hour.
er,在7点到8点之间吧，我们在这儿绕着环形跑道跑步-跑一个小时.
And on weekends we try and...
每到周未我们会...
when we do, we go up to New Hampshire,
当我们这样做了, 我们会去New Hampshire,
and hike in the hills there.
在那儿的山里徒步.
I think with exercise and without the proper diet you're not going to feel good.
我觉得一个人如果只锻炼而不注合理饮食的话，他不会有健康的身体的.
and with proper diet and without exercise you're not going to feel good.
同样，如果光注意合理饮食而不进行锻炼的话，他的身体也不会好到哪儿去.
Yeah, if you do as much training as I do,
Yeah, 如果你每天像我这样锻炼，
or as any triathlete does,
或者像其他三项全能运动员那样训练的话，
you have to be careful about your diet.
你就得好好注意你的饮食.
So, for instance, I have to get 750g of carbohydrates in every day,
So,比如说，我每天必须摄入750克碳水化合物，
um, which is a lot of food.
um, 这就得吃很多东西.
I try not to...
我试着不要...
When I was running today, it was really hard 'cause I ate fat yesterday.
今天跑步时很困难，因为我昨天吃了脂肪食品.
I can really tell the difference.
我真的能感觉出有什么不同.
Makes me feel healthy,
使我感觉身体健康，
feel like I'm doing something for myself.
感觉好像是在为自己做些什么.
It's not easy.
这并不容易.